nuim.ie 2006-12-30

# NUI Maynooth> About NUI Maynooth > Privacy Policy

This statement relates to the National University of Ireland Maynooth privacy practices in connection with the University websites. The University is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. External links to other websites are not always clearly identifiable as such. Within the National University of Ireland Maynooth domain you may find websites over which the University has no editorial responsibility or control. Such sites can include the websites of student organisations etc. While the National University of Ireland Maynooth encourages compliance with this web privacy statement at such sites, please consult the privacy statements of individual sites or contact the persons responsible for those sites, in order to understand the policies and practices under which they operate.

## General statement 

The National University of Ireland Maynooth fully respects your right to privacy and actively seeks to preserve the privacy rights of those who share information with the University. The University will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your permission save in cases where the University is required by law to do so. (e.g. the investigation of a criminal offence or a breach of the University's policies, procedures or guidelines). Any personal information which you volunteer to the University will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988 and Data Protection (Amendment) Act 2003. 

## Collection and use of personal information

The National University of Ireland Maynooth does not collect any personal data about you on this website, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing the University). Any information, which you provide in this way, is not made available to any third parties, and is used by the University only in line with the purpose for which you provided it.

## Collection and use of technical information.

This website does not use cookies, apart from temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor's web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited. Visitors can use this website with no loss of functionality if cookies are disabled from the web browser.

Technical details in connection with visits to this website may be logged by the University's internet service provider for accounting and auditing purposes. 

It is the policy of the University not to disclose such technical information in respect of individual website visitors to any third party (apart from the University's internet service provider, which records such data on the University's behalf and which is bound by confidentiality provisions in this regard), unless obliged to disclose such information by a rule of law. The technical information will be used only for statistical and other administrative purposes. You should note that technical details, which the University cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1988 Data Protection Amendment) Act 2003.

This statement is subject to review in light of any legislative or other indications.

### Further Information and Contact Details

Ann McKeon  
Data Protection Officer  
Humanity House  
NUI Maynooth  
Co. Kildare  
Tel: 01 7086184  
Email: [ann.mckeon@nuim.ie](mailto:ann.mckeon@nuim.ie)

**July 2004**
